K/A

Kyle Atterson

Technical and Design Expert

CONTACT

P: (812) 240-6873

E: kyle.atterson@twicry.com

A: Hymera, IN

L: linkedin.com/in/kyle-atterson/

EDUCATION

Indiana State University

Bachelor of Science (May, 2020)

- Business Administration
- Information Technology
- Management Information Systems

Master of Science (May, 2022)

- Computer Science

SKILLS

- Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, and XD
- Microsoft Word, Excel, Access, and Outlook
- Google Docs and Sheets
- HTML / CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, PHP, MySQL
- Java, C/C++, C#, Python
- Git
- Asana, JIRA, Wrike, ClickUp
- Project Management
- Web and Technical Design
- Creative and Technical Writing

RELATED

- Part-time game designer, working with TTRPGs and products to create design contents and new, full systems.
- Community Management experience dealing with fostering activity across multiple chat programs, social media, and servers.

SUMMARY

A designer with a myriad of experience in modern coding and design programs. I bring a precise eye for detail and a vast knowledge of systems that allows me to create high quality design and technical work to specification. I also have experience in training new staff, working in group-oriented projects and scenarios, and have worked with developing web technology to ensure accessible usability and proper architecture.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Architect, Indiana State University

October 2021 - Present

- Lead web programmer for Drupal CMS in charge of user architecture and ensuring best practices.
- Established partnerships with the web team, campus constituents, and campus governance.
- Trains university staff and creates and provides training documents
- Lead the switch from Google Universal Analytics to GA4

Systems Coordinator, Bursar Operations

August 2020 - October 2021

- Assisted with all technical aspects of Bursar Operations
- Charged with overcoming process failures with existing tasks, designing new, efficient processes.
- Day-to-day university-wide balancing tasks.

Lead Student Web Developer, University Marketing

August 2017 - August 2020

- Managed a team of 3 student developers to handle incoming tickets and resolve university-wide technique questions and issues.
- Promoted from to lead position after 2 years of dedicated work.
- Created basic documentation for training new student developers, including practices and operations.
- Implemented planned changes to the university website, including designing new or migrating sites

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

President, Indiana State University Role Players Guild *May 2017 - May 2019*

- Governed a group of 50+ students to not only share their passions with each other, but breaking out their shells and performing various community services.
- Planned and overseen a yearly college convention, that brought the community to campus to share in hobbies, and make donations in various forms to local charities. Each convention saw anywhere to 300 to 500 people come to play games and support the charities.